kii.com 2015-05-21

# Privacy Policy | Kii

We provide services based on our website and software (“Service”) to mobile application developers. As part of this process, we collect information, including personal and business information from visitors to our website (“Visitors”), mobile application developers who use the Service (“Developers”), and users of applications hosted on our servers, including cloud servers (the same shall apply hereinafter) (“End Users”). “We”, “us” or “our” refer to Kii Corporation, including its affiliate, Kii, Inc. and other affiliates. In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), we describe the information that we collect, use, disclose, and share information, and how we protect your information. Unless specifically distinguished, the practices described herein apply to all Visitors, Developers, and End Users. For immediate access to a particular topic, click on the title of that topic. This Policy is governed by the Terms and Conditions available at <http://en.kii.com/terms>, and is subject to all of its provisions, including its limitation of liability. 

  * Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * How We Share Information
  * Security
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * Our Use of Cookies
  * Children’s Privacy
  * Storage
  * Access
  * Changes to this Policy and Contact information

### Information We Collect

When you visit our website, we collect information about your computer, browser, and web service you are using. We also collect the date, time, pages you visit, and if you linked to our website from another website, and the address of that website. We use such information for statistical purposes that help us design and administer our website and as described below. This information does not disclose personal information that would permit us to identify or locate individual visitors.

## Information We Collect When You Register

When you register with the Service, we will collect certain identifiable information in order to identify and register you as a member of the Service. That information may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other information that you decide to provide to us.

If you are a Developer, We may also collect personal information either provided by you or generated through your use of the Service, including but not limited to information about your End Users, their usages of your applications, and any other data generated or stored with our servers through your use of the Service.

**Note that as a Developer, it is your responsibility to make the appropriate privacy disclosures to your End Users, including disclosures to the effect that a Developer is collecting the personal information from them, that a Developer may share the information with us, and any other disclosures required under the law that relate to the collection and use of your End Users' personal information and sharing of same with third parties.**

## Information We Collect from End Users

Our Service is targeted at Developers. We do not collect information directly from End Users. However, personal information of End Users may be stored on our servers through a Developer’s use of the Service. That information may include:

  * Contact information such as name, email address, mailing address, or phone number
  * Demographic information such as age or date of birth
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, or password
  * Preferences Information such as product or content interests, or communication or marketing preferences
  * Usage activity about how you interact with the mobile application, such what content you viewed and which areas of our website you visited
  * Device specific information such as the type mobile device being used, its operating system, or its universally unique identifier (UUID or MAC)
  * Location-based data such as GPS coordinates, your proximity to cell towers, or wi-fi routers

The actual data collected from the End User and the extent to which it will be shared will depend on the application and the preferences set by the Developer. In order to use our Service, we contractually require all Developers to have in place a privacy policy that discloses what information is collected, how that information is used and whether that information will be shared with us or any third parties. The End Users must affirmatively consent to allow for the requested usage, disclosure and/or access of his or her personal data. Any Developer or application that fails to comply with these restrictions will be removed from the Service. If you suspect an application is violating this Policy or if you have concerns regarding the privacy of your information, you are encouraged to contact our Privacy Officer at:

Privacy Officer  
Kii, Inc.  
1900 S. Norfolk Street, Suite 350  
San Mateo, CA 94403  
United States 

### How We Use Information

You can browse our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. If you choose to register with our website as a Developer, you become identifiable to us and we will collect additional information from you which may be used in the following ways:

_To contact you_ : We may contact you with Service related communications, such as account access details and reminders.

_To provide the Service_ : We use the information we collect to provide our Service and features to you, to measure and improve the Service, and to provide you with customer support. We also use the information to prevent potentially illegal activities and to enforce our Terms and Conditions. All our employees must abide by our Policy and those who violate our Policy are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

We are not in the business of selling customer data. We will not sell, rent, or share information from End Users or Developers without explicit consent, except as described herein or when we believe it is required to do so by law.

_To serve personalized advertising_ : We do not share personal information with advertisers. However, we act as an intermediary between advertisers and Developers who wish you place ads in their applications. When a Developer requests an ad be placed in their application, that request may be sent through the Service to a third party advertiser. Advertisements placed in applications hosted on our servers are personalized for the End User based on information selected by the Developers, such as postal code, gender, date of birth, age, or by keyword. For example, an End User of a baseball themed application may receive baseball themed advertisements. Similarly, location data may be combined with other data so that an End User interested in baseball may receive advertisements for local sports teams nearby. As part of our Policy, we require Developers to disclose what information is being shared with advertisers. Before an application is permitted to serve personalized advertising, it is the Developer’s responsibility to obtain affirmative consent from the End User. Applications who do not receive consent from the users are not permitted to display personalized advertising.

_Information Provision to Third Parties_ : We may share the information we collect from you among us and disclose the information we collect from you to third parties such as outside contractors and service providers that perform functions on our behalf. We provide those third parties with the information necessary to perform the requested service. Any third parties who receive personal information from us will be required to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices to protect the personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. We may also disclose your information to our affiliates and subsidiaries.

_Aggregated Information_ : Notwithstanding any other provision in this Policy, we may share aggregate or de-identified information about users with any third party for marketing, advertising, research or other purposes. For example, we may share aggregate demographic information with any third party about the users of the Service.

_Disclosures_ : We may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, judicial or administrative proceedings, court orders, subpoenas or other legal process. We also may disclose your information to protect our rights and property (including for violations of our Terms and Conditions and this Policy); to prevent against fraud and abuse; to investigate, prevent, or take action with regard to illegal activities, and with regard to potential threats to the safety, rights or property of any person or party (including other users of our website). We also may disclose your information as otherwise permitted by law.

_Business Transfer_ : We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such data transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Policy.

### Security

We are committed to protecting the security of the information entrusted to us. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. In addition, we require any third party working on our behalf who receives personal information from the Service to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices to protect that information from authorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that third parties, including hackers or unauthorized personnel, will not gain access to information stored on our servers despite our efforts. You should note that in using the Service, your information will travel through third party infrastructures that are not under our control.

### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California law, a resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he or she has established a business relationship is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed his or her personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes in the previous calendar year. We do not have an established business relationship with any End User and we do not distribute personal information to outside parties without your explicit consent.

We require all Developers to comply with the California Shine the Light Privacy law. If you are a California resident and an End User of an application hosted on our servers, you may request a list of certain third parties to which the Developer has disclosed personally identifiable information about you for direct marketing purposes in the previous calendar year. You may request this information in writing by contacting the Developer directly.

### Our Use of Cookies

_Cookies_ : When you come to our website, our server sends a cookie to your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. There are two types of cookies: session-based and persistent-based cookies. We also may permit certain third party cookies to be placed on our Website.

  * _Session Cookies_ : Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you while you are logged into our website. This allows us to process your online transactions and requests, and to verify your identity after you have logged in and move through our website.
  * _Persistent cookies_ : Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. We may use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity, which may be combined with other user information.
  * _Third Party Cookies_ : We also may engage third parties, including, without limitation, Google Analytics, to track and analyze non-personally identifiable Website data. We use the data collected by such third parties to help us administer and improve the quality of our website and Services and to analyze usage. We do not have access to or control over these third party cookies nor does this Policy cover such third parties’ use of data.

_Disabling Cookies_ : Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in future. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Website visitors who disable their web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will be able to browse our website although some aspects of the site will not work properly.

_Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)_ : We or the third parties we engage to track and analyze website data may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) to help us better manage content on our website. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages.

### Children’s Privacy

Our website and Services are not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. We also require all Developers to comply with Children's Online Privacy Protection Act or any other applicable laws relating to protection of children’s online privacy by not collecting personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, whether that child is a Visitor, Developer, End User, or other user of the Service, upon receipt of notice from the child or a parent or guardian we will delete that child's personal information from our systems.

### Storage

Our Service operates over the internet through a network of servers located in several countries. While our data is primarily stored on servers located in Japan, the United States and/or China, it is possible that personal information collected through the Service may be transferred to, stored and processed in countries or jurisdictions which do not provide the same legal level of data protection as your home country. By using this Service, you consent to any transfer, processing or storing of information outside your country of residence. We will ensure that if information is transferred outside your country of residence, it will still be treated in accordance with this Policy. In addition, we will ensure that your information is appropriately protected while in transit and while in the destination country.

### Access

When you use our Services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without offering you the chance to opt out of new uses or disclosures of information we collected under this Policy, and we expect most of such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes).

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [privacy@kii.com](mailto:privacy@kii.com) or write to us at:

#### Privacy Officer

Kii Inc.  
1900 S Norfolk Street, Suite 350  
San Mateo, CA 94403  
United States
